From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marbles fan from above
Slightly awake, can't step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Slightly awake, can't ston't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Who just got out of the shower because I got a new shirt
I'll show it a little bit. Let me see. I need to find my lighter and then I'll be all good
One moment. Oh, oh
Okay, oh, it's my it's my vape to I got a vape. Hey, how's everyone doing? How's your how is your Wednesday?
You had a nice day. Wow last night was quite a night though. It was not quite a night
Is anybody here? Hey Trix. Hey Trixie. Anyone was here last night? No
It got pretty wild and I'll say shout out who's will goes shout out who's will goes, you know
and thank you and the I
Hope you're not mad at me or anything like because I
Really I really need people to specify specify, right?
You know what I think he really likes summer. I think he does
As he was like, okay, keep us over and this whole thing, but he didn't want her to be kicked off as soon as I did
He asked her to come back and he did it. Yeah, I don't know but first of all goes like
You're a good friend. Thank you for thank you for really supporting the show last night. I'm gonna be able to now probably
Preparate some more of my equipment. Okay
So very good. How's everyone doing today? Guys the exciting news today, too. I got I found
second I found
What did I find I find something maybe I did I found
Hey, oh I found something outside waiting outside for me today
And it was a delivery. Oh, what's this one that's it goes and
Amazon and I
Want to think spunky she bought me these really cool tarot cards. Well, actually they're not tarot cards
Hey, what's up, John Pablo? It's okay. The old interest still there. I can play that still I can play it at the end of the show
I mean, it's a I miss the logo. Well, you know what I
don't
The local wasn't really like the local is just all it was with the just a magician card. You miss the old Kanye
Okay, well
Go fight it. Are you are you just Canada dry your Canada dry on you?
Don Pablo, I don't know
Oh, let me give you
I'm gonna get the cards. Oh
Excuse me. Hi. Excuse me
Okay, I'm gonna get these cards.
They came in a little black.
I was like, what the heck are these?
I was like, it was like this box,
and I don't remember ordering anything.
And it says, oh, from Spunky, it says,
it says,
says, I can't wait to hear what these cards have to say
for your channel, from Spunky.
Okay, so these are really cool cards.
These are called true crime cards,
and I'm not gonna open up until Spunky gets here,
and then I'll open them up.
Okay
Yeah, so you know I've been having an interesting day pretty good day
How's everyone doing? I've been I was trying to set up today. I was trying to set a power chat for my show
I was thinking okay power chat that probably will just be really easy to set up it goes through stream elements not stream labs
So I'd have to like you know have it on different occasions, right? Hey Trevor
But it was just so it's so complicated. I mean, it's like, oh my god
I do I need to be have computer. It's asking me to like do two two step
Authentication on something and download apps and I don't know. It's getting all complicated
But if anyone knows how to walk me through it, maybe I have the power chat
Account setup. I have this I have the square account set up. I have the
I have the stream elements all set up.
I just don't know how to put them together
and how it's supposed to work,
but anyone knows how that works,
if you could help me out.
Hey, Don Pablo, hey Trevor, hey Jamie's Cowboys.
I'm Jamie's Cowboys.
Jamie's Cowboys and Don Pablo are members.
We actually had a bunch of new members.
Hey, you're Halo, hi Halo, how are you?
Yeah, we had a bunch of new members come in.
I did, you know, me and some other great supports
Been a you know purchasing memberships as a gift and you know so now we have over a hundred memberships
That's pretty cool, and so wow, I mean I would never that's
Mean just that is like I think it's an achievement. I think it's a big achievement, but I do have a lot of other interesting things like
Like how many hours like
thousands of hours of
I'm streaming thousands of hours of streams and I'm putting everything under members only to all the back back episodes
And so if you want to
Take out the back episode. We have a card quite an archive going back to last October. I actually
Those are our private now, but I will get everything moved over to
the members section
So anyway exciting stuff also, you know, I
how many
10,000 hours watch hours in a month. That's impressive for me
May I don't know if I had more ever more before that but it's like 10,000 a month and that's plus
I did delete a lot of streams, you know, so that takes a lot of time for the probably about
Almost half the streams that deleted
The good thing is
Trip kick is streaming my show onto rumble and I'm also streaming my show onto kick. Okay, so
I'll have archives on those shows, right?
I can always go back and watch but it's not online so I don't have to worry about you know
TOS or anything. So that's good news. Okay. I got my I got my Dahmer shades on today
Summer school goes. Yeah
Summer school goes. Yes summer school, you know, but it goes like summer and that's the whole thing
It's like he wanted to chat with he I think he wanted to chat with her
I don't or else he would have just you know been very adamant about get her off the bat
No, he was like, oh five minutes and then he changed his mind. It's like, okay. Well, you just made a deal
This had five minutes, you know, so
You know, I know it is I know he did donate a lot
Yeah, I do I'm a man of my I'd like to make you know, I'd like to keep my word with the deals
And so he he said five minutes
Instead of 24 hours, and I wouldn't have been back until 10 30 night anyway
So she wouldn't have been she wouldn't have missed anything on this show if she was even 24 hours there
You know I didn't want her to be kicked off and
You know it's always always always a hard heavy with some Trevor having some people
You know kicked off the show
Some people it's some people I don't mind some people are some people I kind of do you know, so
Yeah, so hey, hey, what's your tree tricks? Hey tricks. Hey, Trixie there tricks played over here
So let's see. Where's my alien box my box with the aliens. Come on
Always drop in my
Stuff
Okay, well, I don't see it anymore. That's fine. It's a gar
Yeah, we got tricks over here
Tricks you got uh, where's Lola Lola's right there Lola and tricks
I'd like I do like that about my the news version of the song oh here there
Here's the alien card. I'd like a new version of the song. I had you know Lola tricks Rudy Lenore and Marvel's name in that
It's very cute
Haven't seen Marble in a little bit though. I think Marble's gonna have to wander again. Hopefully he goes. Where have I been?
I was asleep today. I slept most of the day and
Was awake a little bit was I went and tried tiktok. I which I mean I've been on tiktok trying to like
get
a thousand viewers, because then I can get my first step towards monetization on TikTok.
I actually had also bought a little bit of ad space, and for my chats to have people
come in the chat, just to see if that would help, and it really didn't.
I had a few people come in, and then nobody even said anything.
So I did track a couple of lives.
I didn't really work out of the five, I'm just like too, I'm not sexy enough or something
like that, or it's just getting started.
I do have about 300 subscribers on TikTok so far, and it's only been like a week, right?
And so I think maybe I'll be 1,000 by a few weeks, maybe I'll be at 10,000, which is official
monetization.
10,000 by, I mean three months, I think three or four months.
maybe faster if I try hard, but, you know, it's interesting.
I don't know what they want me to do.
Like I'm like, quick readings or like short things
or like I'll do shorter streams of course.
I don't know if some people are making a lot of money at it.
Like some people are, but I think it has to do
with like the Tik Tok shop and stuff.
There's like weird stuff going in it too.
The shop looks kind of.
Bad I mean I guess it's all people's own stores their own web stores, and so they will integrate it into the tick-tock and then
Have samples and stuff, but yeah, I'm in here, but have you been okay?
I saw I saw some of your your emails Jamie about that person. I will make sure I do
Hide that person. I'm sorry to get back to you
Hey yesterday. How are you? Did you ask them thing? You see a question mark?
So I will put up the banner in a little bit,
but I'm gonna see if Spunky comes,
because I wanna share these cards with her.
And yeah, my phone.
So it's been quite a day.
Everybody hear me okay?
I've been told I stutter, I talk too fast,
I have a speech impediment apparently.
So if you don't have any trouble understanding me,
You're confused about what you were doing about it,
about that's all?
Well, you're talking about, oh, okay.
I was talking about, well, a bunch of different things.
I was just talking about, right,
then I was talking about TikTok,
which I'm trying to get monetized on.
You need 10,000 members to get monetized, right?
How many do I have?
I'm following 1,085 people.
I'm being followed by 386 people.
Okay, and also something else happened.
I was going through, just rolling through
the TikTok stuff, right?
The TikTok chat, the video chat.
And guess who I ran into?
I ran into Rockstar.
Do you guys know Rockstar?
Rockstar is the guy, he's a streamer in San Diego.
He used to be on YouTube.
Hey, I had a Rockstar family cult.
Now he has, I guess, I went there and he was walking around.
I was like, hey, Rockstar, I was like, oh my God,
because I was the member of his chat.
He's like, oh, I know you, he's like, hey, yeah, he's like,
yeah, I used to be on YouTube a lot.
Now I'm more on TikTok and he went and he liked all my photos.
So yeah, shout out to Rockstar Family Cult that I ran into.
I also found, I ran into some other people there too.
I'm apparently, I've been around on YouTube
where I've recognized a few people.
I think I've recognized about three or four people so just running into them in chats and stuff
So interesting hey school bathrooms
Yeah, so
People are weird this person says to me they say let me say oh there's yeah, there's a
This woman says did you know she writes me
She writes to me. She says, did you know, did you care for a chat to know more about each other as well?
Okay, so I think she wants to know me better.
Like I'm getting like a thousand letters from women. Oh, thank you.
Like if these women and it's like, but they're all the same letters or it's like, oh hi
And then they think goes, oh where are you from and they kind of like all I don't know if it's like spam or something like that
Or like catfish people, but it's like there's just all these women like, you know, I like I'm like more interested in like
No, talking to men right now on tiktok, but where am I? Yeah, where am I from? How am I? There's like all these hearts and stuff
It's like writing me
They have kind of porn star names
Oh, you know what's really cool about tiktok though is that it lets you sign up for a business account kind of like Instagram, right?
And then you can create a message like a custom message and so
I wrote a message about, because the message is says,
I'm a professional tarot reader, YouTube host
with a successful program.
I stream every day, we have a wild time,
I think you'll love it, and you can have a free reading
on me, I'm gonna give the, my URL.
And so hopefully maybe some people will show up
or something, I'm not sure if they're authentic people.
I mean, now I am meeting authentic people,
but I think the first people that were writing me were.
I mean, I just, I have seriously like literally hundreds
and hundreds of emails from people like this going forever.
Yo, Gotti, how are you?
Yeah, and so, you know, VTIC talks
with pretty cool site.
I mean, I don't know if it will work for me,
but I'm talking, I'm working with a chat GPT apparently
on trying to get my 10,000 subscribers
is giving me a little plan.
So we'll see if that works
I'll probably be doing short readings on it
Jamie Lynn Spears reply to my conversation that is bringing Spears sister was going on there. Let's see
What does that say? I?
Don't know. I know it's not working. I
My tablets are just going to every minutes. They really are because they're not
They got the push button doesn't work like half the time
It's like, oh, maybe that's the, I don't know.
It's not working.
Anyway, I'm just gonna turn it off.
Hi, you're a professional asshole.
Yeah, well, you don't need to tell us,
God, do we know that we figured that part out?
Have you seen Sponky? Sponky, she did send me a gift out here today, and I can't wait
to show her. It's going to be really exciting to show her. They look really cool. They're
actually a true crime tarot deck, and so they have kind of true crime, not tarot, but it's
And and so, you know nowadays there's a lot of crime around this and so it's interesting to
See if any of that will pan out so
Okay, now hearing okay
There's some really cute guys on my tiktok
Anyway, okay
Oh, there's Rockstar.
That's Rockstar right there. It's really cute.
I'll tattooed.
Yeah, I think it's interesting.
Okay, anyway, how are we doing guys? Justin is waiting for her to come home. Okay, so she's getting, oh, rail, come on.
Don't say that, that's terrible.
You professional asshole you
Okay, so do I have any
Weed I do have like my baby. Where's my baby? Oh, what was it around here someplace?
My house is a lot cleaner than it was it's not perfect, but it's so much better
But I don't see my I had my baby my tricks. Oh, it's my pocket. Okay
Yeah, haha. Oh, it's not in my pocket. It's just my lighter. Okay. Well, I'll find it later. I did see it recently
Okay, so I
Also have this this is like a crumb rule, but it's a it's a butter. Mmm. Oh
It's a what's that like ice cream flavor that's like really like
It's like sweet. It's like really sweet. It's like, I don't know, but I forgot what it's called.
You're a really professional sweetie pie. Oh, that's Jamie.
Why would she know? Or who? I know you are. What?
Jamie Jamie gets Jamie. It's not even gets along with Alex. Um, Goddy, so it's not saying much. It's not saying much
He's he's such a big heart
It's so kind. I don't think she really does see the best of everyone kind of like I try to but I don't always
especially
Relay, but it's like it's like butterscotch or something. It's like butter. It's like a butterscotch and it's like, um
Kind of a famous ice cream flavor. I'm just for kind of forgetting
Okay, I got it. I'm just joking. I'm just joking. No and God. He is a sweetheart. You are a sweetheart
You guys you want to see my t-shirt though? I think you'll like my shirt
You know that is you see it you read it okay butter pecan yes butter pecan
There's pretty cool
It is vampire
If you don't know who Vampira is, Vampira is, she was one of the, she was like the original Elvira basically.
And she had this like late night program. She wore these really crazy like, you know, long nails.
And this is in the 50s or 50s and everything. She was in Ed Wood's movies. He was in the Ed Wood with that.
It's your ex-girlfriend. Oh, hey, what's up ghost? Yeah, but Edward. Um, he had her and in his movies and stuff
He would out he would make these really weird like campy movies and she would be in it as like some you know, the vampire lady
They basically ripped off Morticia Adams from Vampira, right? She has sleek ways
Discord movie night. Maybe we have maybe we have to see some of that. Maybe it was watch the Edward one Edward or
You know some vampire movie or something because
She was really fascinating, actually, and she was a tragic story, actually, because they
actually developed the character Elvira based on her as well, and then fired her from, she
was supposed to be hosting this thing.
Disco Knight, I don't know, God, are we going to watch Boogie Knights or something like
that?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's Boogie Knights.
Get my girl off your shirt, your, it's your girl.
Wait a minute, come on, say Emma a little bit.
Emma has the vampire vibe, so does Elvira
and you know, Morticia Adams and probably even
Lily Munster a little bit, right?
Lily Munster's more of a right of Frankenstein character,
but.
Along the same lines. Hey, it goes. How are you? It goes. We had a fun night last night. I just want to thank you again
rat Wow
You know, I hope you had I hope you had a fun night though. You're the best that you know vampire
Yeah, but I mean I was a big Elvira fan and when I was like it young like we're really young
My parents used to buy like the beta max cassettes of like her
Specials, you know like where they should play an old B movie and just comment and we love that
Then there was the Elbire movie and I just thought she was really cool. I loved the
character. Now I know more. She's like, uh, you had a blast? Okay, good. Good. Good. That's all that
that matters. That's what matters. So I was like, I think he had fun. I think, I think he had fun.
And that's what matters. So I did too. I did too. And uh,
it was just, it was definitely, it was just the nights, nights for the books, right?
Yeah, so Elvira actually, Vampire actually sued Elvira because she thought Elvira ripped off her character, which they did.
I mean, it was pretty much the same people. Hollywood can be dirty like that, and Vampire did lose the lawsuit.
Kind of had a tragic. I think she did pass away old days. She's better than a Hollywood cemetery, but a little bit of a tragic figure.
Slayer cat somebody in the chat. I don't see Slayer cat in here
And I don't know if they still have a wrench because I don't really remember their name
Is that oh my cat is that that little that eccentric person that might not I think we kicked her off because she might
Have been lying about her age or something
So when can you get a wrench?
You know ghost you've earned it you get one, but uh
The ghost just remember it's like it don't misbehave with it because I don't want to like no take it away
I really want you to have one
but
Just behave with it. You know, it's just like you know, it's just cuz I
Just have to keep the rules for my show, you know, so you'll get what?
Jamie yeah, follow that bird with Big Bird Gotti. It's Big Bird gets it's about Big Bird getting human trafficked by some carneys like well
Not only carneys, but by like basically the social services system
He's like oh well this this bird is living outside on the streets on this sesame street and
and uh, you know
Thinking that it's like, you know, Big Bird is like, you know, like a vagabond
But it was very comfortable outside on Sesame Street in this nest, right? So anyway
Um, yeah, it's kind of so it's kind of sad. I mean, it's uh, you know, it's kidnapped by some
carnies and they're gonna
You know force them to perform sad songs and stuff. Okay, so let me see go here
I won't spoil too much of it. It's a very good movie if you haven't seen it
Yeah, it's a big bird getting human traffic. So then
It should just be a tragedy. So let me see. So there's ghosts. Where's the arbitre?
Okay, there you go
If you know
Arbiter Arbiter Arbiter went went above like really toss a salad
Arbiter really
Really
You know really supported the show last night, so I really want to thank him with that and
The dodo's oh, yeah, the dodo's in the top salad. Yeah, the dodo's that is missus dodo and Donnie and Marie and then so
Like they move big bird in with the with these actual dodo's like there's these big you know these dodo birds
better like all
Just they're kind of I think probably wealthy. They live in a big tree house
But they're kind of dumb right and then big but they won't let big bird see snuff snuff a lot because
You don't know about this. Let me show you got him six petitions walking around
Well, I yeah, like yeah big follow the birds about you know, Goddy comes to Sesame Street and tries to human traffic
Big Bird and all Sesame Street rallies. Yeah, I heard it was Mrs. Finch
Yeah, and everyone rallies to rescue Big Bird
It turns out. It's just me in a in a costume
So yeah, there's big arbitrary guys, you know, it's almost be a
Ghost has a wrench, you know, so any I'm just kidding Gotti, but your God is of course not involved in any of that
I'm sure you would
Never know if he's not a girl snuffle up to guess is this mr. Snuffle up to guess you can get a wrench
No, you cannot know if you if you uh
Labyrinth one night. Yeah, you love labyrinth. I've seen it. I've seen many many times
You remind me of the babe
They pull up because of the hair when I look guys come on. I mean, they're supposed to be there first of all
They're mythological. They're not real. They're the characters. No, I mean, it's like there's all these, you know
Elmo is on crack and you know big bird is you know being pimped
I mean all this about Sesame Street characters meaning a bad end, but they don't and this is just people's like
More than imaginations imagining, you know burden Ernie is
So I'm a gay couple on math and stuff like, I mean, it's like, just gets ridiculous. Am I what?
Am I what, Gotti? I'm just kidding. No, no. But yeah, there's like, and there's, there's actually
a really funny meme I saw, and it's like, look, you know, all the kids like, look, Big Bird is laying
eggs. And they're like, and another one, there's another one. And they're pulling out these like,
these, these like, eggs. And then it's like, you look, and it's like, and there's another one.
And they're all, it's like, it's like anal beads are all attached to this. And Big Bird is like,
It's so dumb. Oh, it's so dumb. Remember that Jamie? That was pretty funny. Dave Chappelle was
pretty funny, but Dave Chappelle went kind of nuts. And now he's not even the same person. In
fact, he's a completely actually a different person. They replaced him with some other actor
that kind of looked like him. And as actor, you can go look him up. It is another actor. You can
tell it looks like him, but it's not him. They just replaced him. That's why people disappear
They're actually replaced and it's like and then they we expect us not to notice if we don't see them around for a while
Then we oh, that's what they look like. How do we know how we not notice a different person is that I see Muppets take my hat
when I was a kid
Because and the Muppets were actually created by Jim Henson as an adult
Kind of cartoon not an adult as in you know
explicit but it's an adult like you know it's supposed to be appealed to more to adults that
they weren't really made for kids they or I think the Muppets were like a late night kind of thing
but in Sesame Street was like we want to I'm doing a panel if summer gets here or if it gets sponsored
otherwise I'll just do one-on-one one-on-one with people but I'll put the link up but yeah
Yeah, I do I'm I'm do I'm only doing the open panels or are only
I'm being sponsored now for like $10 for like three hours with like the advertisements
But otherwise I'll do one-on-one or you know, I can use my discretion if I I want to bring someone on but
Basically like the panels like that everyone wants like the big long ones. It's like, you know, I
Almost a dumb dumb. We come on was ragging on piggy
Well, I mean, it's like have you ever seen I'll know I'm without a skin if he's so useful that
Hello. Hey, buddy
You got me. Yeah, we shut off the YouTube so I've been
Not bad. How are you doing? Well? I was just I always love how you like the the pop culture the vampire
Oh, like, you know all that shit, you know, I mean that I love
Yeah, I was super interested in in it but and I was like I was like I was always like more on a virus side
But then it's like no now I'm older getting to know vampire's story. It really
It was really sad, you know, she was it was sad. That's right
Um, did you watch the Ed Wood movies? You know the the director?
I saw the Johnny Depp one. I've seen clips of them, but I haven't watched one all the way through.
I tried to watch some of them for the nostalgia, but they really are bad. They're so bad, they're good.
You know so much shit.
Yeah, I love that movie. I was always interested in...
Movies about like, you know, there's a movie called who shot Andy Warhol. Oh, it's great
It's good. So Andy. I'm a huge Warhol fan, bro. It's huge. I've been to I've been to the museum twice in Pittsburgh
Mm-hmm, and the first time I went so I love Lou Reed and the velvet underground and when I went it's six floors and
the bottom floor is like a how do I explain this to you is
It's like they redid like the factory a little bit
You know like the place where he worked the factory
That's what they call and they taught you how to do the art like he did
So I made those slides and then it took a picture of me with the background that I made behind me and everything
Like I think you I think you like that a lot. It was it was a lot of fun. Oh cool. Yeah, it really was
Yeah, um, well, let's see. Um, yeah, I uh
Yeah, but I had a good I had a pretty good day. I'm trying just to like, you know test different
I've been trying out tick-tock and stuff like that and trying to figure it out. It's like it's like a little bit
And I never did it. Can you explain to me how like the sponsoring your panel thing works? Yeah, explain. Yeah. Yeah, okay
So I will you know, basically, I'll just take up one guess at a time
But then if people want to do open panel
Have them available to sponsor for like I'll do like a three-hour open panel like last night
We did two of them, you know
And then and then it's like for ten bucks and then it's just the one person pays not everybody
It's just one person or people can come together and then it's like and then that person that
Sponsors they get to like kind of design the banner if they want to that's pretty cool man. That's how you get that idea
Um, well, you know, it's like I just I just felt like the panels like I really like to talk to people one-on-one
Because people's personalities tend to change especially like I noticed like with with certain like women around people's personalities
Will change trying to impress them or something. I don't know. Yeah, it's just I like to have it like you know
And it's like and then it was like they were going on and on and it's like I kind of like can't do do readings during that time people
Would come in and like say oh, it's like this is too busy for readings and stuff. I just thought gotcha
Yeah, and so and so if I'm gonna just be doing like, you know
People but people do like the panels and so oh, let's run it again boys. So the panel has been sponsored tonight arbor at earth
Thank you. Thank you crucible goes for sponsoring the panel tonight
Um, so did he just do it? Did he just did you just sponsor it? Yes. Wow ghosted
yes
Excellent ghost. I've never seen nice. It's on last but last night he last night he did
He just bought so he sponsored it and you know, he you know, what did he put up a hundred bucks?
Is that what it says or says then?
He put up 12 right now. He put up 20 and then he paid five five earlier
So but yeah, yeah last night last night was quite a it's quite an exciting night. It was uh, what happened?
Um, do you have it saved?
Yes, and yeah, they're all safe. So you can go back and watch them. They're under the members, but yeah, he's kind of like I
Don't remember. Oh, no, we know I didn't I don't think I'm a member anymore. I lost my
The guest membership somebody gave me and then I paid it forward and I gave it. I think it was ghost, right?
Wasn't that your panel? Yeah, I'm ghost might have got it. It's his ghost have one. Yeah, I
Arbitr let me see. No, he doesn't have one. I don't know. I don't know that somebody got some someone got it
Ghost I did a yeah, it was the last it was like a couple days ago
I did a guest, you know, whatever. It's called a gift subscription and ghost got it and ghost got it
It must be on his other he must have another account. Wait, do I keep saying ghost? I meant bronze bronze
Yeah, I apologize. I apologize. No problem. No problem
JT, I never thought that day, JT. I always thought you sounded like kind of a white guy.
You know, some sounded black to me.
What did you say?
So now so this is my question so now that ghost sponsors the panel does that mean it's an open panel or no?
How does it? Yes? Yes, it's an open panel. It will be open panel tonight. Let me go come up come up
I'm gonna pin the link and there's the open the link
Do you have a dude movie nights?
what we did on discord a few a few times like when we were on discord and it's like no one's on
discord really anymore but i'm able to um or i'm not i'm actually not able to put it up but
people are if i was to go backstage after the show you know that's what we do yeah so like you get
15 people that's like the amount because you got 10 on the panel and then five can sit backstage
and then you shut off the live and we watch it afterwards we did that um a couple times
Uh-huh. Yeah, I'd like to do that. Is it? No, it's not always open panel
JT I changed it to like, you know, just one-on-one and also guys if you wanted to see that the rules it is in the
It's in the channel description of the good idea how the the clapping and how the how the panning works
But it's the people were saying oh, I was charity everybody to be on the path. No, it's like I was I thought it would be good
You know because there's certain people that you like to have channels and with like a sponsor one and maybe like you know
I think that it is good a good way to build people's channels, too
Like I'll always like yeah, they're linking the chat
But it's like just to have it on the screen and I'll mention a bunch of times
Or if they just want a message up there because people do the TTS
TTS so I have a banner and you know, I'm happy to
Yeah, it goes out goes and I'll see
Yo goes that's really nice to you, bro. Honestly, I'm not I'm not being sarcastic. That's really nice here
Yeah, I figured we might as well decide cuz he white
I
Just open it up. You know for a little bit. Yeah, right? I just really nice to you, bro
No, you fucking you drop 25 bucks for tonight. That's that's really nice here. I dropped a lot more last night
Yeah, that's really nice you last night, too, but I just watching you now. That was really nice to you
Yes, it's up school and I haven't talked to you for a while. I think I mean I forget when the last time I talked to you
Me and you, um, yeah, it's a while ago. It's
Might have been on sorry for you know, I haven't been there probably it's probably on monies or summers
Just working, you know got overtime and just been chilling
I'm watching a lot of films too catching up because when I started hanging out on like youtube channels
I noticed I haven't been watching as many movies. So I've been watching movies lately
Yeah, same with me. I haven't hardly watched any movies, but there are
Movie night, but you never pick a fucking movie. I know
Go ahead. Sorry. No, no, no, I know go ahead
Watch the movie night with us once right ghost on on the ish
Afterwards, are you? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I don't even know what movie it was. You were there though
I totally remember you being there a little bit. I was
But I do remember it. Was it the Civil War night when we watched Civil War?
No, I don't know. I know I know summer cuz I cuz remember I made a big bill that I was like invite me next time
Yes, I mean she actually didn't bite me. I remember you being there one night though. I totally remember I
Didn't lasted the movie dude. I was fucked up watch top gun one time. Yeah, we watched Civil War
the new top gun
No, we watched the original top gun. It was okay. Okay, and then we were gonna do a new one
That yeah, I did see the new one. I you know what I like it. So so I like that
Macquarie the director Christopher Macquarie how yeah
The middle scenes weren't my favorite
But the beginning and the end were awesome because it's my all-time favorite scene with us go ahead. Sorry
No, no, no good
I'm listening by all time favorite scenes when they flew over memory and it blew that fucking little shack up because that was actually like real life
They actually did fly jet over and they filmed that it wasn't CGI at all
How about that was cool. So do you know like Tony Scott the original director of Top Gun?
He killed himself. Did you know that or no?
Did he make any other movies beside that? Yes, he made he is the top action director of the
Yeah, so Tony Scott is Ridley Scott's brother, you know Ridley Scott, right?
Yeah, everybody knows Ridley Scott. Okay. So Ridley Scott's brother is Tony Scott. They have a production company called Scott free
It's a little picture of a bird that like turn a man that turns into a bird and then it says Scott free productions and
Scott Tony Scott worked with Denzel Washington
So all those action movies that you know from the 2000s with Denzel
Man on fire good movie John Q
Dijon yeah, all those all those movies are all Tony Scott films
Unstoppable like there and then he jumped off the Brooklyn Bridge and killed himself in like 2000. Yeah, and so
Tom Cruise was really affected by it and I'll land my plane in about 30 seconds
He said that he doesn't know if he can do
Another top gun unless like there's a director that really he can connect to and Christopher Macquarie
He did like the mission and possibles with him
Him and he's the one that got Tom Cruise to do it. I thought it was good
I thought it was you think it would be you would think it would be Ridley maybe that would be that would be a good
That would be a good story like
Yeah, whatever and then he stepped up. That would be
Really does make Ridley Scott doesn't make good movies, too
Yo, that's I never really thought of that and I don't know why I never thought of it
But how sick would that have been if Ridley Scott? That would have been sick
Hell yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, so we have a Canada dry and PMF can you identify yourselves on panel, please?
But it's got to say Athens has what JT has
Yeah, he killed himself he killed himself
I guess you just seriously depressed or is it was there like we yeah, it was a mental health
It's some kind of woman behind it to be honest
I don't know man, but he was he was definitely the top action director of the 2000s like him and Denzel just fucking
You named her like literally great
His movies the guy is stacked like you just stop making
And the production too, you got to remember Scott free productions. If you look at their
stories or their TV shows that they've done worldwide, it's so good, man.
To taking a pal ham fucking got a handsome
Romance
Movies think of those movies day on your true romance
That's all Tony Scott and then if you look up him as a producer if you're looking at IMDb
Look at Scott free productions him and Ridley Scott all those shows that they did you ever heard of Ken Follett?
It's asked the author. Yeah, he asked you was why did why did he you looked up the story, right?
Why did he why was he so depressed to do that? You know, I mean why were the just depression?
Why did uh, why did uh the comedian? What's his name? We put my favorite comedian um
Who killed himself who hung himself Robin Robin Williams Robin Williams funny that you said that you just knew who I was talking about
I think there was something weird going on
I think it's the same thing with him like it was meant to help because those guys they were
Linkin Park lead singer
That's
Both in beddington and board Dan were both researching like this trafficking
Did Chester Bennington kill himself on Chris Cornell's birthday or something? Wasn't there a weird camera?
I don't know, but he is from my city. It was in my city of where I'm from.
Chester Bennington? He was amazing, bro, and did you know?
Chester and fucking Anthony Bourdain, and there's one other person in that group of people.
Well, Isaac Cappy. Isaac Cappy.
What they did, what they did, Chester Bennington killed himself, though.
I want to look this up.
that is like a kind of their
July 20th guys, July 20th. It was just just past
Yeah, I'm just curious about chris cornell's birthday because
I know chester bennington and chris cornell were close
Yeah, yeah, they really were
Chester and Bennington. Did you know that he had a really bad acidic stomach? Yep. Yep. Chris Cornell was born on July 20th
He was got a heartburn
Yeah, but take so Chris Cornell was your ghost Chris Cornell was born July 20th
Chester Bennington unalived himself with athletic equipment on Chris Cornell's birthday and they were really close like best friends and
He had an acidic stomach that was like
what's the word when it's like really really really bad what you're trying to put together you think
but check this out let me just finish this he did what he loved and it really hurt himself inside
so he said like an interview to get on stage and to scream is what i love to do but it was killing
me inside and he just kept doing it over and over they had to carry him off of performances sometimes
So I think Lane Staley killed himself the same day
Seven years to the day after Kurt Cobain, right
Seven years to the curtain curtain go out like the rest of them. He fuck it now. I mean, that's it's weird. Yeah
Yeah, he went out. Yeah, he did. Yeah, you're right. I
Remember that day
Did you guys remember that morning Danny guys remember that morning when court loader got on MTV news and announced everyone?
I would have been too you either remember MTV. I
Remember where I was remember what I was doing. I would have been like four years old. I think when that happened
I bet there was a lot of people on the panel that remember where they were that morning when they had curb loader
I was like I was 13 years old and so I remember the PE coach came in like what she told us a
No, no, and I didn't know him at all at that time, but then we of course
We were done. I was like sort of getting the music around that time. Yeah, all the girls in my school had this like
thing where they sat down they made like a period during the day where they like lit candles in the cafeteria. That's how like
Crazy, you know, like the girls were about him and stuff. They had like a say like a weird
Remember, it's full. You think that's weird, bro. Hey, when Elvis
Hey, there's some weird shit going on. Yeah, they
Come up Jamie girl weird shit going on
My fucking mom told me she put on a glove and started moonwalking. She never danced in her life
But she heard Michael Jackson died and she started moonwalking. What the hell? Is she happy or sad?
Sad sad
She was a sad moonwalk. Yeah, I listen to Sabbath bloody Sabbath pretty loud in the backyard the last couple
Well, was it today or yesterday today? Oh
We have guests. Oh, we mean by that we jamming out
the
I
Just said you've been so chill like you've been so chill
Well, there's no reason not to be chill right just like in a good mood
I'm just saying you like you've been in a good mood and like you just been like you've been real chill
I'm just trying to give you a compliment. He's true. I appreciate it brother. You're accepted and also, sir
I'm glad that you're up here. Yeah. Yeah, totally. Yeah, you know a lot of shit, you know, right before I sponsored this you joined and I was like, oh, yeah
Definitely want to do this. Yeah, I didn't even know that that was you night psyche. I didn't want to step on summer's toes like
But yeah, let's fucking open it up. Why not? So what happened folks?
Tell me like last night everyone keeps talking about last night last night like what happened. I
Everybody keeps talking about last night. I'm like what the fuck happens
It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny. It was funny
Yeah
Yo, what up Chris, what's going on bro? I'm about to warm it up Chris. That's what I was born to do
Do you watch that video I sent you Chris the one I emailed you
The last yeah, yeah, yeah, I saw that how fucked up is that bro? Yeah, you saw you saw it before I sent it to you
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, I talked to Gina about it. She emailed me and she's just like that's America
You know like that guy was so fucking racist like just and you could see it in his face
Like he felt that shame like fuck. I am fucked and like
That's all unconscious bias. I don't mean but this is shit. This is the shit that gets me going like I get energy like
Fuck you, those headphones are working brother
You could see it in that guy's face that he just looked at those two black people and then and he was like
There's no way that you own this property like you're black and you cannot own this like it was so
And I think that's Florida, right Chris?
Can I try to send the, yeah, I try to send you and Gina,
the Florida stuff.
Oh, that makes me so angry, Chris.
It gets me so angry.
It happened in Ocala, Ocala.
Man, that guy was huge, too.
Did you see how big that guy was?
Yeah.
And he was such a gentleman, man.
Like, he was angry, but like, God, I can't imagine
what that would feel like.
So like you know like UFC fighters like unless they're like crash-offs what she barely hear about but like what they know
They can do that to you. They're the most common people ever
who
If you ever met like a like a train fighter, like they're the most calm people ever
Oh, no, I'm talking about I sent Chris a video and it was a I don't know if it was a state trooper
I think it was a just a regular cop. Yeah, he was a
Deputy gotcha. So it was a deputy in a sheriff's office and there was a couple. Yep
I think he was a deputy though not a sheriff
But yeah, he was and it was a couple a big black guy and his wife, right and they were sitting in their car
just
at this property where a house is half built.
And basically this guy just rolls up on to them,
wants their ID and says like,
you don't own this property.
Like you, that's right because it's nothing from nothing.
Just prejudice, unconscious.
That's the money.
Oh.
Well, you if it's recorded like obviously you sent the video so it's recorded. I died to the fuck out of them boys
It just it just gets me so angry that she that's just embedded inside of like the DNA like Kendrick Lamar says like your daddy
Probably stitches this heritage inside your DNA and he's that's what happens man
Fuck you heard about the three cops that got shot in Ohio today
no, I got to look this up and tell them
I don't know what happened, but
Today, I'll check it out
And this shoot is still at large too
Damn any good cops any still at large. Yep
God damn. Where is that?
Ohio
Wow, yeah, Ohio
I don't go to Ohio, brother
Me you do I so much is it Lorraine three Lorraine police officers? Yes? Yes? Yes, it says the suspect is deceased
Already
Did he kill itself I'm gonna check it out right now. I'm watching the video
Damn this guy ambushed those this guy ambushed. I don't know if that word's okay to you psyche, but this guy of course
Unalived
Yeah, it says the suspect is deceased. It says three officers
shot
This guy ambushed. It's just one guy. He ambushed them
Like he wanted to unalive them fucking insane. It's just gonna get worse and worse everything
Listen, this is just the beginning
Yes, you're absolutely right. It's gonna fuck anyone else. Why'd you put so many bullets in me? It's the same guy that killed three cops
Fuck anyone else who doesn't believe it Chris. You've never been in a real gunfight unless you unload that motherfucker
I mean, this is one shot. Look at these motherfuckers walking. Let's be let's follow the logic though. You send one shot
You're not if you've never even if you shot before if you're in that moment, you're probably gonna miss but keep squeezing that motherfucker
What is the point? Do you understand ghost? That's what we're like Chris and I saying this shit is the beginning people are gonna start going off man
This is police officers
This is what he wanted to do like he wanted the ambush and it's crazy
There's just three of them. There's so many guns in this country. Straight up. So many guns. Yeah, I agree
Every every government official has a gun like every single one of the court office like every single fucking government official does
It doesn't make the rule but is there like a one-off where you might have had three corrupt police officers?
Maybe I never argue that. This says it the best
I've regurgitated your quote. You told me Chris. I mean a hundred times if there was one good police officer
They'd be no bad police officers. I I must have said that a thousand times Chris
I'm just glad for a body came
Where did you see really good thing that we did? Where did you hear that quote Chris? Who told you that?
I don't know I make it up. Yeah, I think so. I've said it a thousand times since I heard you say that
It like clicked in my head like a light bulb. I was like, oh I
Was having a debate with someone the other day the guy was really cool
And he's like, how can you say every police officer's bed? I know
People that and I'm like, are they still police officers? And I'm like, well, actually they're not I'm like, uh, huh?
because you know ghost anytime someone talks about a good police officer they say well actually he's
not a police officer anymore do you know well no i have a different i have a different uh and i
don't i know it's a panel and shit you know i sponsored and shit but if you want to get into it
i'll get into with you because i have a different approach to it so go ahead yeah i think there's
a lot of good people but i think people will follow
the leaders obviously, you know, like that's obviously how it goes and I think
There's a lot of fucking good police officers out there a lot of I think there's none I think there's none
You don't believe there's one good police officer out there at all because of that quote think about that quote
If there was one good police officer, there'd be no bad police officers. Just think about that. Let it sink in
Because when there was one good soldier you're only as good as your worst teammate
Hey, every police officer commits perjury almost once every
Okay, so you're right about that you're right about that I agree with you
I've spoken to four so far ex-police officers two of them are family the other two ex-police officers
Yes, they meaning they did 20 years and retired you understand
What's the name Alex and all four of them said there's no way that they could be a police officer today
Because of the things they've done all four of them said straight up. I've committed
That was before body camps and stuff. They might yeah, that's what I'm trying to say
They've signed their name to false police reports
every day
Yeah, but now but sir, do we not have body cams now everything's recorded, correct? Oh, okay. So what's your point?
Go ahead
So you can't be dirty if it's recorded. We can just look that shit up. Are you watching though?
Like there's still body cam and they don't get yes. Thank you
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about because I've in my life experience. I know it's in adult
I know it's
exception doesn't make the world but in my life I
I think that was some many great police officers actually my brother and my uncle was police officers so maybe um
So
I will
Your brother you said right is blue. Yes, sir. Okay. Yes, sir. Wait. What do you say? I would I would I just said is he blue
Meaning is he cop? I would love for you to answer. Yes, sir. Just just you and him in a personal question
How many times he's committed perjury?
by signing his name to a false police report.
That's what I would love to bring him in here.
You know what I mean, I'm not talking about putting him on blast, I'm just
talking about you and him having a conversation
and being honest with you and I'd love to hear it because
every police officer that I've spoken to said they've done it
every day, every day bro.
But you're talking about four police officers. You've experienced a lot more police than that in your life
Of course, but I'm just
Because Athens you were in debate club you ever heard about like the exception doesn't make the rule
The exception the code. Yeah, that's a really good point. The one good cop doesn't make the rule
They're all good. Most cops are shitty
It's just if somebody steps up
Ghost if somebody steps up and tries to point out somebody else violating someone's civil rights, we're talking about cops they get
Only videos you watch are never watching any of the good videos. Do you want to know that I watch the bad videos?
I actually so I support, you know a lot of different auditors and when I see a cop do good
No, I did hear you. I'm listening. I told them and say thank you when they step up on camera and extend that olive branch
I called them. I called it and you only watch the videos when they break their rights
They're you're only watching dude. You're watching the fucking otter
I don't think you really heard me straight if you're trolling that's cool, but if you're being serious
So what I'm trying to tell you is is when a cop does well on I call them and say thank you
I'm not talking about just that you never watch them do well though. I just
All right
Well, that's why I don't talk to auditors because you obviously you guys don't know what the fuck you're talking about
It's so hard for them on camera to not back up
They're blue. Do you understand like when they were on camera? You could see it
They just won't extend that branch because they don't want to go against the code as there are few bad souls there
Or is there a few bad?
Yeah, I would agree, but you just said that
99% of the cops are bad. No, no, 100% 100%
Well, you even made it one step further, you said 100%
Every single one of them, because listen, no matter what, how many good things you do
If you do a hollible
I thought you were a debater by the way, I thought you went to debate school
I'm pretty sure I've been told about you
That was that was the other one, bud
This shit gets me going like other honestly like I was tired before I was talking to Canada and this shit gets me going because
Do you know how many lives you get fired up? You're gonna be upset about it. Do you know how many lives have been lost though?
Do you know anything you say? Obviously don't know what the fuck you're talking about sir. That's fair. That's fair
I know that it's listen. I only I'm only prejudiced with two things British actors are better than American actors
Every cop is women and every cop is bad my two things that I'm prejudiced about
You'd be surprised you'd be surprised. It's okay to feel it's okay to feel that way
It's okay to have that belief man. Yeah, it's a bad one. No, I know. I know it's really bad though when I say
You and I I've argued with a lot. I'm not an auditor. I'm not an auditor. I'm not trying to strike you at all
I'm not an auditor though just so you know I've done it a couple times just you watch those channels
Do you know I've done it a couple times to feel what they feel you know?
I've filmed the cops myself like there was a trick towards cops
That's the only thing you do so like what I'm watching auditor that fucking crazed a fucking good cop
I mean maybe one time, but of course
Name twice. No, I see I see it every day. Yeah, what are you?
I see it every day though, I got your ass brother. I don't want to watch that
There's a lot of talking about I watch every video that lackluster puts out any new one big
I see a big ghost. I see cops do good things in the videos
But just because they're doing good things in some of the videos
I'm like air-phrasing them. Did you you said a hundred percent of cops?
Listen, just listen that clean ghost listen to me really quick. I already in the corner
Do you not say a hundred percent of cops are the blame? They're bad ghost
Just because a cop does a couple good things on camera doesn't mean he's a good cop. You understand that right?
You could make that argument follow the logic. You make that
You're right. You're two good things doesn't mean I'm a good man
You're right though because the prop is about cops and there's no way I know that and I'm trying to tell you
There's no way I can back up that opinion, right? But that's how I feel inside. That's the prejudice
Yeah
But you're not you're never gonna prove to me. That's correct. You know, there's no way I can you're absolutely correct
And by the way, you're you're not I agree with you. You didn't go to school for it at all
I was I do you agree if you were actually maybe you just had a hundred percent brother. I
Agree with you though. There's no way that I can do better than to say a hundred percent here
What do you want? What are you sipping on tonight? What you got?
Well, I gotta be working up. I mean, what do you got going tonight? I'm gonna donate it money to
Open the panel up. Don't you like liquor though or beer? Are you a liquor guy or beer? I
Don't know sir. Why don't you
Go ahead. You like the hooch. Oh hooch. I thought it was a bird
Over here. Yes, I would agree. I thought you were a makers mark guy. Won't you a makers mark?
Aren't you one?
So well, I mean you want to make I'm not trolling you I'm being honest. Don't you like cognac now?
I didn't say it's rolling us and make you like cognac
Do you like cognac
of all, you know what is he doing I forget who I forget who told me this but I was in my
Let me not be disrespectful. I was told that school and this is a fuck of a very respectable debater
He was actually in college. He was actually in a debate team
This is a fucking video. I that's what I was told
my video
The one with the guy that he and the staffs
Fucked up
I
Thought you like cognac goes you know who I like I am free. Do you watch him sask? He's up in Washington. I
Know you know him Chris. Yes
Who's your favorite Chris?
He thinks doing the most
I watch a lot, but I don't I don't have a necessarily a favorite. Yeah, I got yeah
I got everybody has their own different styles, you know, race is almost at a million men
Who was who was that a million the one the guy that lives by me Sean Paul Reyes
Oh, okay. Okay. He's at nine hundred and sixty thousand
I
Talked to him at the protest and I asked him
I was like did you think you were gonna get this quick so fast and he was like
Because he got arrested in the beginning. That's what like made him popular all those arrest videos
And I had an interesting conversation with him like what they're trying to do
Make things on video that aren't popular. So do you know like how hard that is to like?
What makes them money is when they get arrested and they get yelled at and there's a big scene, right?
What they're trying to achieve is that not to happen so when they walk in and a cop looks at him and says
I know what you're trying. I know what you're trying to do
You're trying to make me crash out
You're trying to make me close the scene and to me logically doesn't that make you laugh like
How can anybody make a cop go crazy? Do you know what I mean Chris?
We don't give a fuck. Well, I don't care. I paid to open up the panel, which is fine
You should give a fuck though because there's been so many
Ways we don't care school at all. You don't care about the lives that are right. You don't care about the lives that are lost
Oh, you're talking about the cops life. You can I'm not talking about them. You care about them
I'm talking about the cops. I don't give up the guy went from trying to put out there. You're not gonna put it out
Shut the fuck up. How many how many cops have told judges? He went from my
All use little words for you Canada, why do you think he doesn't care?
Don't know
That he's a very good person. What about ghost on what about ghost? How do you feel about ghost? Let's get some more
Did she leave see her go so she left
Hit the wall like I've been talking to ghost and all of a sudden you hear his mouth go rude
Really, and then it's like another ghost. You just get a fucking you get a monster. Okay?
Well, if you're gonna talk to me like that, here we go this conversation. You know what's gonna happen
I
Be complimented I'm like, oh, it's you've been really chill lately
As soon as I told him he was cool, right Canada, well, you know, you were cool, too
As soon as I told him he's been so chill lately. He fucking flipped out. Oh, you're talking about uh, uh,
I know what it is. I know what it is. It's your brother
It's because of your brother
It's because of his brother. We're not cops. Why are you up here? I mean, we don't care
Your brother cares. I think it's because your brother. That's what like the person
He says
Now now that he's gone. Let me talk. Oh, let me take the time to talk about bad cops
So the reason why I don't like them because they're dirty and they abuse you and they
Dirty fucking cop. Oh, your brother's a dirty cop
Dirty ghost debater a master debater
Hey master debater, you know, go Canada. Why is he so obsessed about debating master debater?
Fucking school boy. Yeah, you know fucking you want no Canada's fuck. He's fucking hammered, though
You weren't in no debate. What would you like to debate me, sir? Why do you love the day?
matter-of-fact you should just say sorry goes I didn't know what I was talking about
I'm stupid, and you know what delicious man. I'm sorry if you haven't eaten, but this is so delicious
Yeah, so would you like to apologize to me?
He's been killed mission money for 20 would you like money for 20?
You're gonna you're gonna get it tomorrow. This is what I do to you guys
Mike is not working yo, go you're gonna take your money
Yeah, I'll try to do that in the morning if you can do it in the morning
If you can do it in the morning and you send me a text and I'll come out in the afternoon
I got you I try to wake up
Forgot
We got to do tomorrow
Correct, you better recognize remember tonight. I gotta see the back of that on of the the wires you have you have one
You have one display wire right and then you have one of those two pin wires, that's what you said white one
Yeah, yeah, that should be good enough for this computer
Hopefully I just don't know if the display I gotta look at the back of those two computers
I don't know if the display cable is you know gonna fit on the back of that computer
And then I gotta get two white ones
We'll tell you this this motherfucker didn't go to debate school and she did you better get your money back. He's so triggered
It was like a month ago and he was doing the same thing he's doing right now and everybody was talking and just ignore
I mean he was getting so angry
You're just up here kiss my ass though like a man
Let's not do that
Your brother's dirty, bro
You dirty rat bastard pig. That's right. How's my brother? Go ahead next time. Okay. The burden of fruit on you. How's my brother dirty?
Yeah, Mr. Debate School, you're not gonna say nothing. Are you fucking retard?
Oh, this is a new one. Shut the fuck up, boy.
And this is your best debater you got.
So
You do you ever watch direct these videos?
If you if you watch it, there's a new one that he came out with that it just says
This is obviously the dumbest cop in Canada. So there's a new one. That's Canada
Well, how do you like being here?
I'm finna kick you
He went insane fast
Would you like to apologize school no man your brother's dirty if your brother apologizes, then I'll apologize to you, but I want your brother
That's straight up
He's sounding like one of them auditors. Did you sign an oath right every single time?
You know what? I wish that some of them would do how many times do they walk into like a DMV and they're talking to someone and the
Person says I don't like being on camera
They never point out the cameras that are above them and explain to them that they can you know
Get the video on them, you know
It's what I want to do me and sask are gonna get together we're gonna do an audit
Think I'm gonna build a NASCAR. Did you see the one when Sean Paul Reyes got spit in his face the other day?
It was like a week ago
In NASCAR now when I talk about NASCAR we're going back to ordering real quick. I'm gonna talk about it for about two minutes
He went to
This cops his name is Brian Fahey's house and he made a billboard truck
So, you know one of those billboard trucks like in back to the future when they're like elect mayor Goldie Wilson
And they got those trucks
He's got a truck that says like Brian Fahey made 400 grand in overtime. He's a dirty cop and he parks it in
I just went down there. What's going down here?
Why did you kick school? How you guys doing on the spot? You kicked school
Probably kicked yourself by mistake. Oh
Oh, shit somebody paid. How you guys doing? Oh, shit. Why?
Somebody paid
$20 my feet, that's crazy
Well, hi, I
Don't know
And he was up here carrying the conversation. It's so weird when people do that because it's like, I mean